CURRICULUM - VITAE

Alkesh Premaram Mali

• Mobile No: - +91 9998883937

• E-mail : - malialkesh3291@gmail.com

Career Objective: -

Looking forward for a challenging work environment to accomplish the given assignments in the time and to realize the expectation of the organization I workfor, to the best of my capabilities, with the aim of leveraging my skill and experience towards professional growth.

Work Experience: -

Echo Innovate IT.

Laravel Developer (Nov 2021 to till date)

- Working on analysis, design, development, and management of web on windows based software applications to manage, test and develop distributed client/server, Internet and Intranet applications on heterogeneous environments.
- Experience in developing ui applications using html5, css3, jquery, ajax, and javascript.
- Built custom ui, widgets and application logic using ui and mvc architecture.
- Interact with client to gather requirement. Analyze requirement and develop functionality accordingly.
- Working on various types of projects like health care web application

Reliance Digital Ltd.

Customer Relationship Manager (Nov 2020 to Oct 2021)

- Improve Customer Service Experience.
- Working on SAP/CRM for fetching Customer detail.
- Handling Customer Queries, Inquiry, Complaints, Billing and DOA cases of all Brands.
- Support in establishing a strong business relationship.

Farmahar Private Limited

IT Support Executive (May2020 to 31 Oct 2020)

- Improve Customer Service Experience.
- Support in establishing a strong business relationship.
- Analysis data and compile the further reports for improvement.
- Handling back-end server for update the daily in master data.
- Resolving all the IT related issues of our stores.

Personal Skills: -

Confident, Team Player, Analytical, Reasoning ability, Excellent presentationskills, Good writing skills.

Software Proficiency: -

• **Programming Languages:** C, C++, Core java, Dart

• Make up Language: HTML, XML

• Framework: Laravel

• IDE'S: Eclipse, Microsoft Visual StudioCode

• Scripting Languages(client-side): PHP, AJAX, Java-Script, JQuery

• Presentation Definition Language : CSS

Database Management Systems: MYSQL

Operating Systems: Windows, MacOS

• Source Control: Github

Educational Qualifications: -

MSc.IT(Mobile Application & UI development), From Gujarat University Animation Department pursuing.

Bachelor of Computer Applications (BCA), From JG College of Computer Application (Sept-2020) with First class.

HSC from Nutan Vidya Vihar School (Mar-2017) with 64.00%.SSC from

Solaris Public School (Mar-2015) with 65.00%.

Work Projects:-

Bankers:-

Bankers is a web based applications allow healthcare professionals to keep track of their patients' conditions and progress during their treatment. The web apps can store medical test results for patients, which doctors can access at any time moreover patient can also order medicine through this web application and also make an appointment with the doctor and lab at home or specific address.

Quick Coach:-

QuickCatch is a sports application that allows players and coaches to easily communicate with each other. Also the player can chat in a group as per his purchased subscription plan.

Docoholic:-

Docoholic is the web application for exporters. Helps exporters automate pre & Post shipment documents also helps convert more deals with realtime Export deal insights and significantly reduce cost with other document automation.

Academic Project: -

Project: - Online Medicines Sales Web Application

- The project "Online Medicines Sale" is a PHP web application that will allow the users to place order for various medicines by uploading their prescriptions.
- The application will also provide them with other medical products, discounts and offers.

Personal Details: -

Present Address : A-303 Tulsi Residency,

Opp. Krishna Bunglows, GST

Crossing Road, New Ranip,

Ahmedabad- 382480.

Date of Birth : 28th September 1999

Gender : Male

Languages known : English, Hindi, Gujarati Hobbies

: Internet Surfing, Playing cricket

Listening songs

Life theory : "Do work with Perfection & Confident"

Declaration: -

I guarantee you that my managerial skills will be distinctive competencyresources to your Organization.

I am willing to meet you, if you need further clarification about my resume.

Yours Faithfully,

Alkesh Mali